You're home. Forever.
Vivarium is a science fiction, thriller, mystery
film directed by Lorcan Finnegan.
A young woman and her fiancé are in search of the perfect starter home.
After following a mysterious real estate agent to a new housing development, the couple finds
themselves trapped in a maze of identical houses and forced to raise an otherworldly child.
Gemma, played by Imogen Poots.
Tom, played by Jesse Eisenberg.
Young Boy, played by Senan Jennings.
Older Boy, played by Éanna Hardwicke.
Martin, played by Jonathan Aris.
Baby, played by Côme Thiry.
Vivarium is a 2019 science fiction psychological thriller film directed by
Lorcan Finnegan, from a story by Finnegan and Garret Shanley.
Shanley also wrote the screenplay.
An international co-production of Ireland, Denmark and Belgium, it stars
Imogen Poots, Jesse Eisenberg, Jonathan Aris, and Éanna Hardwicke.
The film follows a couple (Eisenberg and Poots) who are forced to care for a mysterious
humanoid creature while trapped in a strange, vivarium-like neighbourhood.
It had its world premiere at the Cannes Film Festival on 18 May 2019, and was
released in Ireland on 27 March 2020 by Vertigo Releasing.
The film explores themes of baby, suburbia, suburb, trapped, cynical.
The tone is dark and mind_bending and thought_provoking.